# Vibudh Rathore

https://portfolio-vib.netlify.app/

# **ABOUT**

As a passionate web developer, I have knowledge in ReactJs, PHP, Laravel and MySQL technologies with industry working experience,. My academic background in MCA has equipped me with the necessary skills in software development, database management, and problem-solving.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

### Full-Stack Developer, Hrbotics

2023/07 - 2023/09 | Noida, India

- Created a HR(Company's dummy) website using ReactJs.
- Used API's for data integration in the project.
- Used Ecwid to make website templates.
- Worked in live project, enhanced UI components.

### Web Development, InternPe

2023/07 - 2023/08 | Virtual

- Learned thoroughly about front-end and back-end technologies.
- Developed static web pages using React.
- Made some minor projects like calculator, contact form etc.

# **PROJECTS**

#### Admin Panel [7]

2024/04 - 2024/05

- Created using PHP and MySQL
- User registration with validation for fields like email, password.
- User login with authentication by using session.
- User roles and permissions for authorization.
- CRUD operations for user data.

#### DGital 🛮

2023/07 - 2023/08

- Developed a responsive web application using React.js, HTML5, CSS3, to create a modern user interface.
- Worked on RESTful API integration with the frontend for data exchange.
- Utilized React Router for client-side routing.

#### **GROCO** 🗷

2023/04 - 2023/06

- Grocery Store Management System created using html, css and javascript.
- Dynamic cart using javascript where you can add or remove products.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Master of Computer** Applications,

Galgotias University 2022 - 2024 | Gr. Noida, India

# Bachelor of Science, CSIMU

2019 - 2022 | Kanpur, India

# **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- jQuery
- React js
- PHP
- Laravel
- MySQL
- Python

#### **STRENGTHS**

- Quick and Good Learner
- Self-motivated team player
- Never Give up attitude

# **CERTIFICATES**

- IBM Web Development Fundamentals [2]
- Udemy Improving Software Dev Productivity ☑
- Hackerrank Python basic certificate 🛮
- Udemy JavaScript Practicals crash course ra